http://www.piezo.com/pages/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
We respect your privacy! Any and all information collected at this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed. Any information you give to Midé will be held with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways to which you have not consented. A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard your personal information is described below. If you have any questions, please don't hesitate to contact us.
Resale or disclosure of information to third parties
Midé does not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any personal information collected at our site, including membership forms or email lists.
Browser information collected on the Web site
Our Web site logs are not personally identifiable, and we make no attempt to link them with the individuals who actually browse the site.
Google Adwords
We use tracking technologies from Google Adwords. We guarantee that your personal information will never be sold or used irresponsibly at any time. We do not store your purchasing information on any of our hard drives.
Use of cookies
www.mide.com uses google analytics to collect visitor data and analyze traffic on our site. This information helps us understand customer interests and helps us improve our website. When you visit our site, the pages that you look at, and a short text file called a cookie, are downloaded to your computer. A cookie is used to store small amounts of information. This information is collected for traffic analysis only. The cookie does not contain personal details. Depending on the browser that you use, you can set your preferences to block/ refuse cookies, and/ or notify you before they are placed.
Personal information
At Midé, we intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. In general, you can visit Midé on the Web without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may need information from you, such as your name and address. It is our intent to let you know before we collect personal information from you on the Internet.
If you choose to give us personal information via the Internet that we may need—to correspond with you, process an order or provide you with a subscription, for example—it is our intent to let you know how we will use such information. If you tell us that you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes. We do keep track of the domains from which people visit us. We analyze this data for trends and statistics, and then we discard it. We have implemented these practices for the Midé Home Page (www.mide.com).
Information security and quality
We intend to protect the quality and integrity of your personally identifiable information. We have implemented appropriate technical and managerial procedures to maintain information that is accurate, current, and complete. We will make a sincere effort to respond to your requests to correct personal information inaccuracies in a timely manner.
Business relationships
The Midé site may contain links to other Web sites. Midé is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
0
